

DMITRY KULBEDA

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

CONTACTS SKILLS LANGUAGES

- 🤳 +375 29 162 85 24 🔹 Javascript/Typescript 🔹 Russian Native
- @ iforox@gmail.com React/Redux English C2 (EFSET)
- Ryke_VL Angular/RxJs
- GitHub Git/GitLab

ABOUT ME

I am actively seeking a position as a Frontend Developer. I have 1.5 years of commercial experience and developed 10+ projects during my time at the RSSchool course. My primary technology stack includes TypeScript, React and Angular. Currently, I am specifically looking for opportunities focused on React applications.

EDUCATION

Sep. 2012 - June 2016 Belarusian State College of Electronics

Technical Programmer

Sep. 2016 - Jan. 2021 Belarusian State University of Informatics and Radioelectronics

Engineer Programmer

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jan. 2021 - Jule 2021 RSSchool

Frontend Course. Projects that I've developed during the course

you can find here.

Nov. 2021 - Feb. 2022 Aimobi Apps

Developed web version of mobile app OnPhone. Worked with **React/Redux**, used **jest** and **storybook** for testing and **react-intl**

for multiple-language support.

Dec. 2022 - Feb. 2024 Targsoft

2 months of experience working on outsourced projects focused on React, along with 1 year of Angular development on an internal project intended for future release. Technology stack included **React, Jest, Angular, Angular Signals, RxJS, Docker and**

Tailwind CSS.